<?xml version="1.0"?>

<book>
<page type="intro">
<text>MiscItemsAndBlocks Guide


- This guide book will show all new recipes added by MiscItemsAndBlocks. It will also give some small descriptions for all the changes and additions.

- If the recipe for a block/item is blank it means that it is disabled in the config.
</text>
</page>

<page type="contents">
<text>The contents of the guide book</text>

<link>
<text>Blocks</text>
<icon>xp_storage</icon>
</link>

<link>
<text>Items</text>
<icon>guide_book</icon>
</link>

<link>
<text>Other changes and additions</text>
<icon>writable_book</icon>
</link>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Xp Storage block</title>
<text>The Xp Storage Block allows a player to save the xp levels in a safe location. The Xp Storage block does not have any upper limits of how many levels it can store. The xp storage block is blast proof and also when it is broken by a player it saves the levels in the block so they are not lost. 
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>xp_storage_block_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Trash Bin</title>
<text>The Trash Bin blocks does what you would expect it deletes any items that are put into it. The trash bin slowly deletes the items so it is possible to take items out if you change your mind. 
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>trash_bin_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Disarm Trap</title>
<text>The Disarm Trap is a block that works kinda like a pressure plate by that it is activated when someone steps on it but the disarm trap disarms the player that steps on it and throws all the items.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>disarm_trap_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>



<page type="text">
<title>Silver Ore</title>
<text>The Silver Ore is a ore which spawns at Y 14 and below but it is very rare. Silver ore itself is useless but it can be smelted into silver ingots.
</text>
</page>
<page type="furnace">
<text>Use</text>
<recipe>silver_ore_use</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Stone Stair</title>
<text>Stone Stairs works exactly as any other type of stair the only difference is that these look like a normal stone block.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>stone_stair_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Cardboard Box</title>
<text>The Cardboard Box is a kind of cheaper type of chest or item storage. But the cardboard box can also be picked up and moved without losing the inventory.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>cardboard_box_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Worktable</title>
<text>The worktable is like a upgraded version of the normal crafting table. It will save the crafting grid and it also has a internal inventory where you can store items. The worktable will automatically use any items from the internal inventory to craft it they are available.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>worktable_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Dice</title>
<text>The dice is a item which was added to be used together with the game pieces. The dice can be dropped on the ground and it will change to a random number between 1 and 6.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>dice_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Speed Block</title>
<text>The speed block is a block which will speed up any entity travelling on top of it. So it can be useful for item or mob transfer systems.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>speed_block_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Game Pieces</title>
<text>The game pieces are blocks which is meant to be used in games. The game pieces can be right clicked to push it one block in that direction. The game pieces can also be pushed up blocks and on top of other game pieces of the same colour. And the games pieces can be found in five types: Blank, Red, Blue, Green, Yellow. To get the different types of game pieces you combine a blank game piece with that colour of dye.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>blank_game_piece_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Pillar</title>
<text>The pillar is a block very similar to the game pieces by looks but the pillar can not be pushed like the game pieces. The pillar can also unlike the game pieces connect sideways and the pillar is meant as a decorative block.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>pillar_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Mill</title>
<text>The mill is a machine that can be used to make bread making more efficient by allowing you to make 1 to 1 bread. You can put wheat into the mill and it will make flour which can then be smelted into bread. The mill is a machine which is meant to not be automated so you can only store 16 items, cant input or output items with hoppers and you cant use shift-click.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>mill_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Squeezer</title>
<text>The squeezer is a machine which is meant to be used to make different types of fruit juice. Some of the juices you can make are: Apple, Orange and Carrot.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>squeezer_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Oven</title>
<text>The oven is a new type of furnace made specially for food. The oven uses coal to heat up and will slowly lose the heat over time but the higher the heat is the faster it will cook the food.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>oven_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Item Pedestal</title>
<text>The item pedestal is a decorative block where you can place any item on top of it by right clicking it with the item you want to display. To get the item back right click with a empty hand on it.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>item_pedestal_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Table</title>
<text>The table is a decorative block. If the table is placed next to other tables they will connect forming one table. The table can also be right clicked with a red carpet to add table cloth.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>table_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Paint Block</title>
<text>The paint block is a block which uses the colour system called RGB (Red, Green, Blue) You can chose between millions of colours on the block by using the different types of paint brushes added to the mod.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>paint_block_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>One Way Glass</title>
<text>The one way glass does exactly what it sounds like. When placed it will face the player with a glass side the other side of the block will be shown as stone.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>one_way_glass_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Computer</title>
<text>The computer is a minecraft computer where you can do different things like private chat, play games and other things. 
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>computer_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Storage Block</title>
<text>The storage block is a huge storage block which has 800! inventory slots where you can store items. The storage block also stores its contents so it can be picked up and moved.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>storage_block_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>




<page type="text">
<title>Work In Progress</title>
<text>This guide book is still a work in progress so more info will be added soon. </text>

</page>



</book>
