<?xml version="1.0"?>

<book>
<page type="intro">
<text>MiscItemsAndBlocks Guide


- This guide book will show all new recipes added by MiscItemsAndBlocks. It will also give some small descriptions for all the changes and additions.

- If the recipe for a block/item is blank it means that it is disabled in the config.
</text>
</page>

<page type="contents">
<text>The contents of the guide book</text>

<link>
<text>Blocks</text>
<icon>xp_storage</icon>
</link>

<link>
<text>Electrical blocks and items</text>
<icon>charger</icon>
</link>

<link>
<text>Items</text>
<icon>guide_book</icon>
</link>

<link>
<text>Other changes and additions</text>
<icon>writable_book</icon>
</link>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Blocks</title>
<text>In this part of the guide all the normal blocks will be shown.
</text>
</page>
<page type="blank">
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Xp Storage block</title>
<text>The Xp Storage Block allows a player to save the xp levels in a safe location. The Xp Storage block does not have any upper limits of how many levels it can store. The xp storage block is blast proof and also when it is broken by a player it saves the levels in the block so they are not lost. 
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>xp_storage_block_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Trash Bin</title>
<text>The Trash Bin blocks does what you would expect it deletes any items that are put into it. The trash bin slowly deletes the items so it is possible to take items out if you change your mind. 
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>trash_bin_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Disarm Trap</title>
<text>The Disarm Trap is a block that works kinda like a pressure plate by that it is activated when someone steps on it but the disarm trap disarms the player that steps on it and throws all the items.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>disarm_trap_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>



<page type="text">
<title>Silver Ore</title>
<text>The Silver Ore is a ore which spawns at Y 14 and below but it is very rare. Silver ore itself is useless but it can be smelted into silver ingots.
</text>
</page>
<page type="furnace">
<text>Use</text>
<recipe>silver_ore_use</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Stone Stair</title>
<text>Stone Stairs works exactly as any other type of stair the only difference is that these look like a normal stone block.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>stone_stair_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Cardboard Box</title>
<text>The Cardboard Box is a kind of cheaper type of chest or item storage. But the cardboard box can also be picked up and moved without losing the inventory.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>cardboard_box_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Worktable</title>
<text>The worktable is like a upgraded version of the normal crafting table. It will save the crafting grid and it also has a internal inventory where you can store items. The worktable will automatically use any items from the internal inventory to craft it they are available.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>worktable_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Dice</title>
<text>The dice is a item which was added to be used together with the game pieces. The dice can be dropped on the ground and it will change to a random number between 1 and 6.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>dice_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Speed Block</title>
<text>The speed block is a block which will speed up any entity travelling on top of it. So it can be useful for item or mob transfer systems.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>speed_block_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Game Pieces</title>
<text>The game pieces are blocks which is meant to be used in games. The game pieces can be right clicked to push it one block in that direction. The game pieces can also be pushed up blocks and on top of other game pieces of the same colour. And the games pieces can be found in five types: Blank, Red, Blue, Green, Yellow. To get the different types of game pieces you combine a blank game piece with that colour of dye.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>gamepart.number.0_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Pillar</title>
<text>The pillar is a block very similar to the game pieces by looks but the pillar can not be pushed like the game pieces. The pillar can also unlike the game pieces connect sideways and the pillar is meant as a decorative block.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>pillar_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>TV</title>
<text>The TV is a decorative block and does not have any actual functions.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>tv_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Mill</title>
<text>The mill is a machine that can be used to make bread making more efficient by allowing you to make 1 to 1 bread. You can put wheat into the mill and it will make flour which can then be smelted into bread. The mill is a machine which is meant to not be automated so you can only store 16 items, cant input or output items with hoppers and you cant use shift-click.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>mill_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Squeezer</title>
<text>The squeezer is a machine which is meant to be used to make different types of fruit juice. Some of the juices you can make are: Apple, Orange and Carrot.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>squeezer_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Oven</title>
<text>The oven is a new type of furnace made specially for food. The oven uses coal to heat up and will slowly lose the heat over time but the higher the heat is the faster it will cook the food.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>oven_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Item Pedestal</title>
<text>The item pedestal is a decorative block where you can place any item on top of it by right clicking it with the item you want to display. To get the item back right click with a empty hand on it.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>item_pedestal_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Table</title>
<text>The table is a decorative block. If the table is placed next to other tables they will connect forming one table. The table can also be right clicked with a red carpet to add table cloth.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>table_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Paint Block</title>
<text>The paint block is a block which uses the colour system called RGB (Red, Green, Blue) You can chose between millions of colours on the block by using the different types of paint brushes added to the mod.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>paint_block_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>One Way Glass</title>
<text>The one way glass does exactly what it sounds like. When placed it will face the player with a glass side the other side of the block will be shown as stone.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>one_way_glass_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Computer</title>
<text>The computer is a minecraft computer where you can do different things like private chat, play games and other things. 
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>computer_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Storage Block</title>
<text>The storage block is a huge storage block which has 800! inventory slots where you can store items. The storage block also stores its contents so it can be picked up and moved.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>storage_block_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Dice Stand</title>
<text>The dice stand is a block version of the dice. The dice stand changes number when right clicked or when receiving a redstone signal. 
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>dice_stand_res</name>
<size>two</size>
</recipe>
</page>



<page type="text">
<title>Wireless Redstone</title>
<text>The wireless redstone block does what it sounds like it can be linked up with another wireless redstone block using data chips then when the sending part is receiving redstone it will transmit it to the receiving.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>wireless_redstone_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Wireless Item transfer</title>
<text>The wireless item transfer block can be linked up with another using data chips and will then send item from one end to the other storing it in the internal inventory in the receiving end.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>wireless_item_transfer_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Ghost block</title>
<text>The ghost block is a non-solid block which can be hidden as another block by right-clicking it with the block you want to hide it as. The ghost block can also be locked to the player that placed it by shift-right clicking it.  
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>ghost_block_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Electrical blocks and items</title>
<text>In this part of the guide all the blocks and items related to the power system added to MiscItemsAndBlocks will be shown.
</text>
</page>
<page type="blank">
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Machine Part</title>
<text>The machine part is a block used for crafting other electrical machines but it can also be used as a decorative block.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>machine_part_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Energy Storage Cube</title>
<text>The Energy Storage Cube is a block which can store energy and output it. The energy storage cube will output from the orange side and input on all other sides. The energy storage cube can be rotated by clicking on it with a wrench and shift-right-clicking with a wrench to set it to the opposite side of the one clicked.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>charger_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Solar Panel</title>
<text>The solar panel will generate power to adjacent machines and cables that accept power. The solar panel will only generate power if it is daytime, it has clear sight to the sun and it is not raining.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>solar_panel_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Wind Mill</title>
<text>The wind mill will generate power if it is located above Y 80 and the heigher above that it is the more power it will generate.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>wind_mill_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Coal Generator</title>
<text>The coal generator will use coal as a fuel to generate power.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>coal_generator_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Electric Furnace</title>
<text>The electric furnace will use power from a adjacent charger point at it or connected power cables to smelt items/blocks like a normal furnace,
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>electric_furnace_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Power Cable</title>
<text>The power cable can be used to transfer power from energy storage cubes and power generating blocks to machines and other blocks that accept power input.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>power_cable_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Metal Press</title>
<text>The metal press is a machine which allows you to create cheaper iron plates then the normal crafting recipes.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>metal_press_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="text">
<title>Lens Bench</title>
<text>The lens bench allows you to customise lenses which can then used in laser blocks.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>lens_bench_res</name>
<size>two</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Laser</title>
<text>The laser can be used to transmit power, redstone or be a automated killing system by using custom lens where you can select length, power, colour and more.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>laser_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Laser Receiver</title>
<text>The laser receiver can be used to receive the power that is transferred through a laser by placing it on a block that accepts power or redstone.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>laser_reciver_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Mining Station</title>
<text>The mining station is a automated mining block that uses power and a pickaxe. The mining station can be set to sizes between 1x1 to 11x11 and it can be told how deep it should mine. The mining station will also be affected by some enchantments on the pickaxe like unbreaking, fortune and efficiency.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>mining_station_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Teleporter</title>
<text>The teleporter can be linked up to another teleporter using data chips. When linked up the teleporter can be used to teleport to another location by pressing sneak above it when it has atleast 100 power and has a valid data chip. The receiving teleporter can also be disabled by applying a redstone signal.
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>teleporter_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


<page type="text">
<title>Drill</title>
<text>The drill is a electric mining item which can be recharged in the Energy Storage Cube. The drill also has 3 modes: Normal(1x1), Bigger (3x3) and Biggest(5x5)
</text>
</page>
<page type="crafting">
<text>Recipe</text>
<recipe>
<name>drill_res</name>
<size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Circuit Board</title>
        <text>The circuit board is a item used for creating most items and blocks in the power system.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="blank">

    </page>

    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>circuit.basic_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>

    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>circuit.advanced_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Module Connecter Part</title>
        <text>The Module Connecter Part is a crafting item used for making diffrent power releated transfer blocks.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>moduleconnecter_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Solar Cells</title>
        <text>The solar cell item is a crafting item used to making the solar panel block.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>solarcells_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Turbine</title>
        <text>The turbine is a crafting item used to making the wind mill block.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>turbine_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Batteries</title>
        <text>The batteries are a electric item which can be used to transfer power from different machines and for crafting. It is three different batteries: Battery(Can store 16 power), Bigger battery (Can store 32 power), Advanced battery(Can store 64 power).
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>battery_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>bigbattery_res</name>
            <size>two</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>advancedbattery_res</name>
            <size>two</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>

    <page type="text">
        <title>Electric Shears</title>
        <text>The electric shear is a electric version of the shears which can be recharged in a Energy Storage Cube.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>electricshears_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Electric Bow</title>
        <text>The Electric Bow is a bow which runs of power and can be recharged in Energy Storage Cube. The electric bow does not need arrows it uses power from the bow instead of arrows.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>electricbow_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Power Upgrade</title>
        <text>The Power upgrade can be used in some energy storage blocks and machines to increase the max energy storage.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>powerupgrade_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Wrench</title>
        <text>The wrench is used to change the mode of power cables and to rotate the Energy Storage Cube.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>wrench_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Iron Plate</title>
        <text>The Iron Plate has 2 main forms the normal Iron Plate and the Hardened Iron Plate. The normal Iron Plate is used for making the most basic power related items and blocks. The Hardened Iron Plate is used to make the more advanced power related items and blocks.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>ironplate.1_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>

    <page type="furnace">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>plate_res</recipe>
    </page>

    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>ironplate.2_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Heat Drill</title>
        <text>The Heat Drill is a kind of upgraded version of the Drill. The heat drill will smelt any block mined and can also smelt blocks on right click. But the Heat Drill does not have a multi size mode as the drill has.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>heatdrill_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Floating Platform Placer</title>
        <text>The Floating Platform Placer is a tool that will place temporarily blocks below the player and will also reset the players fall distance to prevent fall damage.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>floatblockplacer_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Antifall Chestplate</title>
        <text>The Antifall Chestplate will slow the players fall down to remove fall damage. When holding shift you will fall quicker but will still not take fall damage.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>antifallchestplate_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Info Display Screen</title>
        <text>The Info Display Screen is a wearable screen which can be worn as a helmet and will show the current power percentage of the current item being used, the current armor if it is power related and it will show the power of the info display screen.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>infoscreen_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Data Chip</title>
        <text>The Data Chip is a item used to link diffrent wireless devices together. The Data Chip can store data from one machines and will show which machines data it is storing. The data of teh Data Chip can be remove by shift-right clicking.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>data_chip_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Lens</title>
        <text>The Lens is used in the laser. The lens can be customised in the Lens Bench where you can set the color, power, strength and other options.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>lens_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>



    <page type="text">
        <title>Items</title>
        <text>In this part of the guide book the rest of the items will be shown.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="blank">
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Xp Extractor</title>
        <text>The Xp Extractir allows you to extract xp levels and store them in bottels as Bottle o´ Enchating. When using the Xp Extractor you have to have atleast 1 xp level and 1 glass bottle.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>xpextractor_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Silver Ingot</title>
        <text>The Silver Ingot is a metal which can be found at Y 14 and below.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="furnace">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>silver_ore_use</recipe>
    </page>

    <page type="text">
        <title>Silver Sword</title>
        <text>The silver sword one-hit kills most normal mobs but it does not affect players or boss mbs. The silver sword also counts the amount of mobs you have hit and the last mob you hit.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>silver_sword_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Silver Bow</title>
        <text>The Silver Bow is a bow that does alot of damage to any mob. The silver bow cant use normal arrows it can only use Silver Arrows.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>silverbow_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>silver_arrow_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>

    <page type="blank">

    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Power Armor</title>
        <text>The power armor is a very power full armor set which gives different effects from the different armor parts. Some of the effects are:
    Helmet: Night vision and water breathing
    Chestplate: Allows creative like flight.
    Leggings: Speed boost
    Boots: Jump boost
also when wearing the full set of armor you will be immune to fire damage and you will also receive effects when damaged.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>powerarmor_helmet_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>powerarmor_chestplate_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>powerarmor_leggings_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>powerarmor_boots_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>
    <page type="blank">

    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Cardboard</title>
        <text>Cardboard is a item used when crafting circuits, cardboard boxes and other things.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>cardboard_res</name>
            <size>two</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Tomato</title>
        <text>Tomato plants are added by MiscItemsAndBlocks. Seeds for the tomato plant can be found when breaking tall grass. The tomato can be used to make tomato sauce for pizzas and the tomato can also be used as normal food.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Use</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>tomatoseeds_res</name>
            <size>two</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Flour</title>
        <text>Flour can be made by putting wheat into a mill. The flour can then be used to either craft pizza base for making pizzas or it can be smelted into bread.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Use</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>pizza_base_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Cheese</title>
        <text>Cheese is used to make pizza and can also be used as food.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>cheese_res</name>
            <size>two</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Pizza</title>
        <text>The pizzas is a very good food type when cooked. The pizzas can be made with any type of vanilla meat.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>pizzaraw.3_res</name>
            <size>two</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>


    <page type="text">
        <title>Paint Brushes</title>
        <text>The Paint Brushes are used on the paint block and can be used to get the different colors which uses the RGB Color system which gives around 16.000.000 different combinations of colors. The different colored paint brushes will add that color to the block and the paint copy will copy the color and paste it on shift right click. The Paint editor will allow you to chose a color through a gui when shift-right clicking the paint brush.
        </text>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
    <text>Recipe</text>
    <recipe>
        <name>paintbrush_2_res</name>
        <size>three</size>
    </recipe>
</page>

    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>paintbrush_res</name>
            <size>two</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>paintbrush_0_res</name>
            <size>two</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>
    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>paintbrush_1_res</name>
            <size>two</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>

    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>paintbrush_3_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>

    <page type="crafting">
        <text>Recipe</text>
        <recipe>
            <name>paintbrush_4_res</name>
            <size>three</size>
        </recipe>
    </page>



</book>
